<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pei-Han</title>
    <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pei-Han</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://hsu-ph.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an Information Systems student specializing in data science and AI applications! I&amp;rsquo;m an Information Systems student focusing on data science and AI applications. I love solving real-world problems with data and exploring the infinite possibilities of AI.&#xA;In my spare time, I am also a visual enthusiast who loves photography. Through the lens, I capture the wonderful moments of life, and I look forward to using my professional knowledge to bring changes to education, health and other fields, so that technology can truly benefit society!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Game Experience</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went with a friend to see a regular season NBA game in Boston to watch the Celtics, and it was truly &lt;strong&gt;an unforgettable experience&lt;/strong&gt;! The atmosphere was &lt;strong&gt;electric&lt;/strong&gt; right from the start, with fans wearing green jerseys and chanting slogans. (Of course, we wore green too!)The moment the players entered the stadium, the crowd erupted, and the cheers were deafening. Being there, I felt an indescribable sense of &lt;strong&gt;unity&lt;/strong&gt; that you simply can&amp;rsquo;t experience on TV.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A leisurely stroll in Boston Park: a perfect blend of history and modernity</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Walking around Boston Common is a relaxing experience. This park is like the heart of Boston, surrounded by skyscrapers, but once you enter it, it&amp;rsquo;s like you&amp;rsquo;ve entered another world. Not only are there lush green grass, old trees, and lakes, but there are also a lot of people coming and going at a seemingly leisurely but rhythmic pace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Walking here, you can really feel a kind of historical deposition. This place is not just a park, it is also a witness to Boston&amp;rsquo;s history. From an early military training ground to the scene of protests before the American Revolution, this place has seen many significant events. As I walked past the monuments and statues, I could still feel the past. But at the same time, Boston Park doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel old at all. Every day, people from all walks of life - students, office workers, families, and even tourists - come here to walk, exercise, and relax. There are people sunbathing on the grass, flying kites, and sitting around chatting about gossip, and the atmosphere in the park is both relaxed and lively. This kind of everyday life gives the whole place a modern feel.&#xA;I especially like the blend of nature and the city. The skyscrapers reflecting on the lake, the leaves and grass turning colorful in the fall, it&amp;rsquo;s like entering a painting. This kind of feeling is hard to find in the city, giving me a sense of relaxation and ease. After walking around for a while, I realized that the rhythm here is very special and not as rushed as in other cities. In Boston Park, there was no rush. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re resting on a bench, taking a walk, or just lying on the grass reading a book, everyone is enjoying the moment, and time seems to have slowed down. All in all, Boston Park is a very suitable place for a casual stroll and relaxation. It has both historical depth and modern vigor. Whether you come here for a walk, to sit and relax, or to gather with friends, you can feel a relaxing and pleasant atmosphere. A park like this is a great place to slow down and recharge your batteries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/new-year-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/new-year-nyc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New York City during the holiday season feels like stepping into a magical snow globe. The streets are alive with the sparkle of Christmas lights, the air smells faintly of roasted chestnuts, and everywhere you turn, there’s something that makes you stop and smile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spent an afternoon at Bryant Park’s Winter Village, sipping on hot chocolate while wandering through the cozy little stalls filled with handmade trinkets and festive treats. The chilly weather couldn’t dampen the warmth of the season—street performers singing Christmas carols, small cafes offering peppermint lattes, and the buzz of cheerful conversations made it impossible not to feel the holiday spirit. It’s those little, unexpected moments that make this time of year so magical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Follow me, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/pei-han-hsu-264139214/&#34;  class=&#34;external-link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;linkedln&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
