<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plog on Pei-Han</title>
    <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/tags/plog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plog on Pei-Han</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://hsu-ph.github.io/tags/plog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NBA</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://hsu-ph.github.io/images/IMG_6449.JPG&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;Watching Celtics Game&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;NBA Game Photo&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went with a friend to see a regular season NBA game in Celtic and it was an unforgettable experience!&#xA;The atmosphere was electric right from the start of the game, surrounded by loyal Celtic fans wearing green jerseys and chanting slogans. (Of course, we wore green too!!) The moment the players entered the stadium, the crowd erupted and the cheers were deafening. Being there, I felt an indescribable sense of unity that you just can&amp;rsquo;t experience on TV.&#xA;The game was full of excitement and tension. Saltik&amp;rsquo;s players played their hearts out on the court, and every defensive and offensive play, especially a few key three-pointers, brought the atmosphere to a climax. Every time a Celtics point was scored, the crowd would roar with cheers.&#xA;Watching soccer is not just about enjoying the game, it is also a great memory to share with friends. We discussed tactics, predicted the score, and even joked about some of the players&amp;rsquo; special moves. After the game, we even went to the neighboring stores to buy some souvenirs. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll be looking for another opportunity to support Seltic in the future - after all, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing like being there!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
