<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiences on Pei-Han</title>
    <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/categories/experiences/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiences on Pei-Han</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://hsu-ph.github.io/categories/experiences/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NBA Game Experience</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/nba-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;NBA Game&#34; src=&#34;images/IMG_6453.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went with a friend to see a regular season NBA game in Boston to watch the Celtics, and it was truly &lt;strong&gt;an unforgettable experience&lt;/strong&gt;! The atmosphere was &lt;strong&gt;electric&lt;/strong&gt; right from the start, with fans wearing green jerseys and chanting slogans. (Of course, we wore green too!)The moment the players entered the stadium, the crowd erupted, and the cheers were deafening. Being there, I felt an indescribable sense of &lt;strong&gt;unity&lt;/strong&gt; that you simply can&amp;rsquo;t experience on TV. The game was full of &lt;strong&gt;excitement&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;tension&lt;/strong&gt;. Celtics players played their hearts out, and every defensive and offensive play, especially a few key three-pointers, brought the atmosphere to a peak. Every time the Celtics scored, the entire crowd roared with excitement. Watching a game isn’t just about enjoying the sport; it’s a chance to share a memorable experience with friends. We discussed tactics, predicted the score, and even joked about some of the players&amp;rsquo; special moves. After the game, we went to neighboring stores to buy some souvenirs. This night truly made me appreciate the joy of live sports and the &lt;strong&gt;camaraderie&lt;/strong&gt; it fosters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Game Experience</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/projects/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/projects/food/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;food-delivery-app-associated-with-food-supplier&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Food Delivery App associated with Food Supplier&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#food-delivery-app-associated-with-food-supplier&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&#xA;  [Introduction]&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#introduction&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a food order system based on Java Swing. The System includes farm, food company, the branches of the companies, and normal customers can order food. Within this digital realm, customers can explore menus, place orders, and savor a variety of culinary delights. Farms , companies, and their branches, in turn, manage their offerings and branches efficiently, creating a harmonious link between the agricultural source and the end consumer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A leisurely stroll in Boston</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Boston Common&#34; src=&#34;images/DSC00785.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Walking around Boston Common is a truly relaxing experience. The park feels like the heart of Boston, surrounded by towering skyscrapers, but once you step inside, it feels like you&amp;rsquo;ve entered a different world entirely. The park is full of lush green grass, ancient trees, and serene lakes, and yet, it&amp;rsquo;s constantly alive with people coming and going at what feels like a leisurely yet rhythmic pace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I walked here, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but feel the weight of history in the air. This park is more than just a green space—it&amp;rsquo;s a witness to Boston&amp;rsquo;s storied past. From its origins as a military training ground to its role in protests before the American Revolution, Boston Common has been the site of countless significant moments in history. As I strolled past the monuments and statues, I could almost hear the echoes of the past. And yet, despite its rich history, the park doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel old at all. It&amp;rsquo;s a vibrant, modern space where people of all ages and backgrounds come to unwind. Students, office workers, families, and tourists—everyone gathers here to walk, exercise, or simply relax. I saw people sunbathing on the grass, flying kites, and sitting in small groups chatting about anything and everything. The atmosphere is lively but relaxed, a perfect blend of energy and calm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christmas in New York</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/new-year-nyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/new-year-nyc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;New York City during the holiday season feels like stepping into a magical snow globe. The streets are alive with the sparkle of Christmas lights, the air smells faintly of roasted chestnuts, and everywhere you turn, there’s something that makes you stop and smile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spent an afternoon at Bryant Park’s Winter Village, sipping on hot chocolate while wandering through the cozy little stalls filled with handmade trinkets and festive treats. The chilly weather couldn’t dampen the warmth of the season—street performers singing Christmas carols, small cafes offering peppermint lattes, and the buzz of cheerful conversations made it impossible not to feel the holiday spirit. It’s those little, unexpected moments that make this time of year so magical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
