<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boston Adventures on Pei-Han</title>
    <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/series/boston-adventures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boston Adventures on Pei-Han</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://hsu-ph.github.io/series/boston-adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A leisurely stroll in Boston</title>
      <link>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://hsu-ph.github.io/posts/bos-common/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Boston Common&#34; src=&#34;images/DSC00785.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Walking around Boston Common is a truly relaxing experience. The park feels like the heart of Boston, surrounded by towering skyscrapers, but once you step inside, it feels like you&amp;rsquo;ve entered a different world entirely. The park is full of lush green grass, ancient trees, and serene lakes, and yet, it&amp;rsquo;s constantly alive with people coming and going at what feels like a leisurely yet rhythmic pace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I walked here, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but feel the weight of history in the air. This park is more than just a green space—it&amp;rsquo;s a witness to Boston&amp;rsquo;s storied past. From its origins as a military training ground to its role in protests before the American Revolution, Boston Common has been the site of countless significant moments in history. As I strolled past the monuments and statues, I could almost hear the echoes of the past. And yet, despite its rich history, the park doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel old at all. It&amp;rsquo;s a vibrant, modern space where people of all ages and backgrounds come to unwind. Students, office workers, families, and tourists—everyone gathers here to walk, exercise, or simply relax. I saw people sunbathing on the grass, flying kites, and sitting in small groups chatting about anything and everything. The atmosphere is lively but relaxed, a perfect blend of energy and calm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
